Reeve Jonathan Aranha

Profile

Full-stack engineer and data analyst capable of translating client's requirements to working solutions. Experienced web developer adept at designing and building engaging UI/UX. Focused on customer service, worked to develop key relations, built strategic partners and effectively managed operations and logistics. Experienced with public speaking, conflict resolution and peer-to-peer feedback and support.

Employment History

IT Support Coordinator at BRG Infotech, London

May 2023 — Present

- First point of contact for systems errors and troubleshooting
- Assisted users with IT-related issues and provided technical support, reducing daily ticket resolution time
- Effectively managed the help-desk with a task based approach to meet SLAs and team KPIs
- Managed assigned escalations and reported to line manager when required
- Provided suggestions and potential solutions with a warm and friendly service to all queries from customers

Client Relations Manager at Homesight UK, London

August 2022 — August 2023

- Scheduled and attended meetings with Scheme Managers to present NHS-funded domiciliary services to residents
- Exceeded revenue target by 34% for a single clinic
- Reached out to and registered 5,500+ new patients in under a year
- Conducted health talks and presentations at various venues to raise awareness on the importance of auditory and visual health

Operations Supervisor at Just Eat Takeaway.com, London

February 2021 — August 2022

- Supervision of the warehouse and a process-oriented approach when implementing daily core operations' tasks
- Scheduled and conducted Performance Management sessions which reduced the 'at risk' employees from 67% to 32% over 3 months
- Implemented new process to reduce inventory costs and saw an effective reduction of 40% over one month, effectively reducing operational costs
- · Responded to queries and solved issues faced by couriers, new starters and restaurant partners

F&B Sales Associate at Renaissance Hotel, Bengaluru

Details

London

United Kingdom

+44 7570339252

reevearanha@gmail.com

Links

Personal website LinkedIn

Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Python

Microsoft SQL Server

Microsoft Office

Power BI

Salesforce

Asana

Jira

- Participated in the Marriott Sales training program to understand the company's method of sales and service
- Planned weekly sales calls to attend meetings with general managers and senior management to offer them F&B banqueting and corporate catering services
- Engaged in hotel show-around for clients and successfully closed and managed one animal-themed children's birthday party for mother's and their children, and one dinner event for a group of 50 persons celebrating an auspicious Indian festival
- Main point of contact for New Year's Eve 2020 event at Renaissance hotel with contact details shared across all company media and print

F&B Associate at Lake Powell Resort, Arizona

May 2017 — November 2017

- Managed catering for annual general meeting of board members
- Modified milkshake recipes to create widely popular versions to bring in repeat customers
- Engaged in up-selling of items and venue and assisted bar manager with stock takes and materials purchasing

Sales Associate at BUZ Management and Marketing Consulting, Dubai

January 2016 — March 2016

- Created city-wide plan for registering F&B outlets and 5-star hotels to take part in the Dubai Food Festival 2016
- Distributed marketing material and help setup social media templates for all participating F&B venues
- Achieved personal KPIs for venues contacted and meetings secured and strategically worked with team mates to drive brand recognition

Education

MBA Digital Marketing and Finance, University of West London, London

September 2020 — October 2021

BA Hospitality and Tourism Management, University of West London, London

September 2016 — May 2019

Courses

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate, Coursera

October 2021 — December 2021